Thank you for watching!
The Shitala and Himura teams face off for a chance to win a gorgeous prize!
A little late in the game!
The Himura team has a slight lead now!
Who will win?
Let's play the next game!
Mr. Himura, please!
Let's play!
Head Gun Gun Lead Day!
A familiar game on the show.
A message game in which the participants are asked to convey a message using only their mouth movements.
The team that can convey the theme farther
The team that can convey the message the farthest wins points!
We're having an entertainment event right now, but we don't have enough people, so it's like a small, compact company launch.
Kimura's team will start with their members. You bet your asses on it.
I'm talking to you! Wait a minute... I heard that.
I just heard you say "bonkers." Something's wrong over here.
Endo likes curry.
I don't know.
Endo likes it.
Endo likes...
Endo loves...
Okay, that's it.
Can I take a picture of this?
I can do it! I can do it! I can do it!
I love endo.
I love it.
Endo...
No, no, no, don't take it. Don't take it.
Daisuke.
Daisuke Endo. Daisuke Endo
Yes, yes, it's over.
Okay, we're done.
Let's start with Kuromi's presentation.
Endo is Ishidera.
Ishidera? I wonder if he lives in Ishidera Park or something.
Let's see...
Daisuke Endo.
There must be someone named Daisuke Endo.
And Mr. Himura...
I love Endo.
And what's that?
You got the message.
I love Endo.
I can do it.
Come on, Tom, let's hear it.
Endo loves curry.
There's no curry.
No curry.
Well, basically, everyone knows Endo.
Endo got it.
Now let's see how far the Sitara team can take it
Back to the moon!
"I love you, I love you, I love you.
I'm going back to the moon!
I love you!
Moon facing home!
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK
We're going back to the moon!
We're going back to the moon.
go back to the moon
facing
yes ok yes end yes end yes end yes end
I love you sea urchin
I love it! I love it.
Sakurai
I love you, sea urchin!
I love them.
First, first, first.
I love, I love, I love you!
That's it... that's it... that's it... that's it... that's it.
Hakuhinkan.
Next.
Hakuhinkan!
Angry!
Hakuhinkan.
Iron Man.
Whitepin Hall.
Hakuhinkan.
Icing.
The end.
Yes, over.
Yes, over... Yes, stop!
Yes, Yoda, what did you hear?
Icing bar
Come on, Shitara-san
It's Hakuhinkan!
It's Hakushinkan.
You didn't get the message here.
It's Hakuhinkan.
I love sea urchins.
Sea urchin.
It must have someone's name on it.
I'm going back to the moon across the street
I'm going back to the moon
The moon is about to return
The moon is coming back...
Okay, so what's the correct answer?
No, no, no. No, no, no.
The Moon Returns, Across the Street
The moon is about to return
The moon is coming back.
Stupid MG
I was wearing headphones.
You're right about the moon going back.
It's so hard to say "yang-ki" after "yang-ki," because the mouths are almost all the same.
I'm sorry...
It's "across the street"...
mukae
across the street
It's free, isn't it?
It's an icing bar at the end.
We did it!
I don't think we lost at all.
The team that won the second round was the first team to challenge
Yakiniku Set Meal
Yakiniku
Yakiniku Teishoku
What are you talking about?
Yakiniku
Yakiniku teishoku
Yakiniku Teishoku
Yes, yes, excuse me.
Okay, let's go.
Yes, let's go
various foods
yakiniku
grilled meat
let's go with that Let's go with that.
Yes, OK.
grilled meat
taikei kukumura
taiiku
Mimura
fire village
grilled meat
the worst
some how, it's a fire village
yes OK
taiiku (gymnastics)
grilled meat
uu uu uu
ah ah ah ah
great food, great sun
flame
grilled meat?
Himura?
Maybe it is.
Tell me yours.
What are you talking about?
Say yours.
Last Last again
great education
OK OK
End. End.
Go ahead
Yakiniku Himura
Let's go!
Yakiniku Himura! the education system
I didn't get it.
You didn't get it. You didn't touch it.
The correct answer is...
Yakiniku Teishoku. What's this?
That's why yesterday's move was "yakiniku".
The yakiniku came back.
What's this?
Dad wasn't bald, but Grandpa was.
You're right.
I like it.
Can the Himura team surpass Yakiniku Himura?
Please, start!
Tokyo Sky Tree!
Tokyo Sky Tree
Tokyo
What! I don't know!
Special?
Tokyo
Instant?
Sky Tree
My favorite!
Yes, yes, yes!
Diner
I love it!
What a stupid thing to say!
Tohoku Tohoku
I love
I love it.
Seriously, I don't know.
Do you mind if I do my hair?
Love.
I made a mistake.
Northeast.
Touhoku.
I love Northeast.
Love
Love.
Okay, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Finished!
I wonder how far they got.
Groovy.
Come here, shampoo.
She's going to change everything.
Come on, shampoo.
And I won't repeat it.
I don't know if she gets it, because I don't repeat it.
I love Tohoku.
Love
I love Sousou
Tokyo Sky Tree
So here is the win!
Yay!
Now it's time for the second half of the entertainment corner!
Tonight's entertainment is going to be a star-studded affair!
Let's go!
Who's next?
Who?
All right, let's hear it for the road.
Why, why, why, why? Why, why, why?
asa
demand
sand
how many of these
those
Why are you singing this
Why the nasal harmonies
He's so handsome.
He's so cool.
He's cool.
That's cool.
What does the harmonica do?
Oh, oh, oh, smell
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm not doing 37 spare time!
I'll get someone on the pod with the title you.
Laser Raman RJ's
You must be RJ.
I thought you were asking me to do that.
So I practiced it in the bathtub.
That's what you mean, isn't it?
I was listening to it in the bath and kept peeping at it.
That's great.
That's nice.
You sounded like a good-looking guy.
No, of course not.
He's so cool.
Oh, my God.
He's cool.
Really?
They're gonna sell me fake paintings and stuff.
That's awesome.
Seriously, Mr. George is coming out here.
I want to hear it one more time.
Just one more time.
Just the harp, if you don't mind.Okay, just the harp.
I loved you.
So thank you for the addition.
Thank you very much.
Okay, are you ready?
Let's see who's next.
Ratz-A-Duster.
Masayuki Suzuki.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for your hard work.
Wait a minute.
That's great.
I wonder if it's an offer from the beard.
You left the beard alone.
Wait a minute.
Kazuyuki Suzuki.
You've been very busy.
Very busy.
He's a big seller, isn't he?
You look great up close.
Is it?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
You do it without hesitation.
Thanks to my sunglasses.
I can do anything.
Sunglasses can hide
I can hide my embarrassment.
I'm going to ask you to take off your sunglasses for a moment.
Can I just have one more thing?
One more thing.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I like it. It looks kind of nice in a hotel like this.
That's great.
Okay, then. The next one, please.
Go ahead.
What's this? What's this?
It's the Fear All-Back.
It's you.
Oh!
Thank you for watching!
Amazing!
Female 1 Excessive Reversal
I'm not sure about the original.
I'm not sure what this is based on...
It's a music video for a song called "Fear All Back"!
Fear All Back is popular?
I didn't know it was popular.
Fear All Back!
Seriously, guess my fear.
I guessed it.
That's not so bad.
I'm getting my hair done with a gun.
Oh, my God.
It's relentless, isn't it?
But you've got to blow on it.
Yes, sir.
I made a mistake.
It's the wind.
But you're still cute even when you're exposed to the wind.
It's true.
The music video has a really serious face.
I kept looking at Haruka-san, trying to keep a straight face.
I had my eye on you.
I was able to keep a straight face.
That's for sure.
Now who the hell is Otani?
And then there was Rust.
Rust!
Who's missing?
Let's go with Rust!
Let's go to the last one, please.
I see...
Which one? which one?
Mr. Nishikawa
Ah, Nishikawa-san.
There it is.
Thank you for watching!
No!
Oh no!
Congratulations!
Nishikawa, why is Tsutsui in this?
What's wrong with Tsutsui? I couldn't understand.
Your hair looks good like that, but the way you apply the wind, it's unforgiving.
Mr. Nishikawa, you were instructed to go to the max level.
This song is for wind.
Normally 3 is normal, but I set it to 5.
How did you do?
I found something new about myself.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you did it.
It's like a character from a video game.
Like in Resident Evil or something.
He's so cute!
I don't need "cute.
You don't want cute?
What do you want to be called?
It's Nishikawa-san.
It's Nishikawa...
Let's play the last game
Salary Magic Game
Guess the number of times you fit the theme
The rhythm game is to guess the number of times you fit the theme and look back in time to the music so as not to be the same as the other players.
The team that is closest to succeeding wins points!
First, the Nimura team challenged with five members.
It's nice to see so many different people here.
That's right.
Mr. Himura is a Bakabon
Not "Bakabon.
Mr. Himura is doing it.
I thought you were doing something like that. I thought, "Mr. Himura, you're not Bakabon, are you going to do something like that?
Then, for the Nimura team, the question is who is a natural.
Let's start with a natural person.
Let's start the music!
The staff has chosen everything.
Go for it!
Okkun picked it.
Okkun picked it
go for it!
too bad
I thought you were first, Mr. Himura.
I'm about number three.
Mr. Himura, number 3?
You're first, right?
I'm number one?
You're the most natural.
You're number one, Mr. Himura.
I'm No. 1?
Natural people are natural because they don't look back.
I'm number one.
I thought I was number one.
What do you mean you can't?
I could do it!
Did Endo tell you that?
Endo's a natural.
I thought he was a bit of a jerk.
And then, number two, no one turned around.
What a waste, I should've been there.
And then number three, Mr. Himura and...
I went.
And fourth, Inoue, right?
Look at this lineup.
Hey, hey, hey!
It's a long time ago now...
Hey, get your uncle, you know, these guys.
More than these guys. No more than these guys.
I'm not a natural.
Kubo was the last.
You said Kubo's solid.
That's not true.
Kubo's totally solid.
Look at this group.
This is tough.
I want to play with all my hands!
The last game!
Will Shitara's team succeed?
I think so.
This guy...
He's taking them to a hot spring.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's go!
The subject is!
A crass person!
Crass!
Let's go! Let the music begin!
Thank you for watching!
Yeah!
We lost!
We did it!
No, we gave up first place to two crass people.
I was so worried, so worried.
Yeah, I thought it might be me, the crass one.
No, I think we've talked about that before.
I think we've talked about that before, too.
But Yoda? I knew it!
I'm sure!
Definitely Yoda.
No. 1 is Yoda.
It's got to be Yoda.
Yoda.
If these two don't go, we're screwed.
I'm screwed.
This game's so hard. This game is so hard.
Yay!
Team Himura wins!
I don't like it.
Go for round three!
I love this team.
I love you!
Now that the Shitara team has no chance of winning...
If they all succeed at the Chocolate Disco...
If they all succeed in the Chocolate Disco, I'll turn the game into a rollercoaster!
Will it be a miracle that all the team succeeds?
If not, the team will lose the game.
The last subject is
Chatterboxes
Talking
Start the music!
Wait a minute
Uh...
hmm
Mm-hmm.
Yay!
Congratulations!
Three in one, three chatterboxes.
Shut up, here. Three people.
No, I just thought that's the kind of image you want to project on this show, so I thought I'd give the number one spot to you.
They talk a lot. Yes, they do.
When you two are next to each other in the car, you talk all the time.
I was number 3. If we were in a tree, it would be so loud that I'd be competing with you for the number 1 spot.
In a tree?
It's beautiful.
So, the winner of this year's New Year's party is...
Jayman Himura.
The first prize, as I mentioned.
What's this?
Take a picture of the team you bought it from and put it in a jigsaw puzzle.
Jigsaw puzzle!Jigsaw puzzle.
There are only ten in this world.
And these misty boxed strawberries.
A box of these for each of you.
One box is not enough.
Because I told you before.
Because Ume said so before.
Oh, no.
It's in this misty box from Senbikiya.
It's 10,000 yen class.
I wonder if it's a relief.
Nogizaka46 35th single to be released
New selected members will be announced in the next program
Hello, I'm Yuna Shibata. This is Haruka Kaki.
I'll tell you what I like about Yuna. I like the transparency of her bangs.
I love the color of her mouth. No, she's cute without it.
Thank you. Thank you. I like it here.
I like the length of her hair. Her cheeks are cute and smooth.
I like the way it feels. I like her eyes. I like her make-up.
I love her nose. I love her neck. I love her hands.
Subscribe to my channel. Bye-bye.
She's so cute.
by H.